let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the commercial capital of sri lanka?",
    answer: "colombo",
    options: [
      "colombo",
      "Sri jayawardanapura",
      "Gampaha",
      "Kalutara"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the legislative capital city of Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Sri Jayawardanapura",
    options: [
      "Sri Jayawardanapura",
      "colombo",
      "Hambantota",
      "Matara"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "what is the longest river in Sri Lanka??",
    answer: "River Mahaweli",
    options: [
      "River Mahaweli",
      "River Kalani",
      "River Kalu",
      "River Walawe"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the currency of Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Rupee",
    options: [
      "Dollar",
      "Yen",
      "pound",
      "Rupee"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " How many districts are there in Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "25",
    options: [
      "22",
      "23",
      "24",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the main religion of Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Buddhism",
    options: [
      "Islam",
      "Hindu",
      "Buddhism",
      "Burger"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the tallest mountain in Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Piduruthalaga",
    options: [
      "Gonagala",
      "Kirigalpothha",
      "Bathalegala",
      "Piduruthalaga"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What animal appears on the flag of Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Lion",
    options: [
      "Tiger",
      "Eagle",
      "Lion",
      "Elephant"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Name the first Executive President of Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "J.R Jyawardana",
    options: [
      "J.R Jyawardana",
      "R.Premadasa",
      "S.W.R.D Bandaranayaka",
      "D.S Senanayaka"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "When did Sri Lanka receive independence?",
    answer: "1948",
    options: [
      "1948",
      "1946",
      "1947",
      "1949"
    ]
  },
];